<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>matsch</title>
    <link>https://matsch.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on matsch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 15:24:24 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://matsch.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Concerning Projects</title>
      <link>https://matsch.dev/posts/concerning-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 15:24:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matsch.dev/posts/concerning-projects/</guid>
      <description>Over the next couple of days, I will be updating the projects page. The updates mainly consist of experiments and projects that I created during my studies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://matsch.dev/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 23:31:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matsch.dev/projects/</guid>
      <description>Melody Helpr Melody Helpr is an app that tries to help with creating melodies from scratch. It is meant to be used in companion with the Open Source recording software Ardour. You can create new melody sequences, double or halve them, recreate at any point and finally transfer the created sequence from Melody Helpr back into Ardour to further work with it.
Find this project at my GitHub.
What&amp;rsquo;s that, Arcanoid?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://matsch.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 22:46:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matsch.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey there. My name is Matthias. I&amp;rsquo;m a graduate in Media Design (B.A.) and passionate about using web technologies to create art and tools to improve everyday life. I also like to tinker with different programming languages from time to time. Some days, I go out into the woods where I enjoy a relaxed solo walk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://matsch.dev/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 22:14:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matsch.dev/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome. I&amp;rsquo;m glad you found this place. On this blog, I want to share my thoughts on technology, music and a few other topics. I try to post in a regular manner. Come back any time to see the updates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>